meqelle.info 2012-06-22

# Meqelle

**INTRODUCTION**

This Privacy Policy tells you the types of information we collect when you use our Sites or Services, how we use that information, and the instances in which we share your information. 

**SUMMARY OF KEY PRINCIPLES**

We thought it would be helpful to set out briefly the key ways in which we use your information and how we seek to protect privacy. Of course, you should read the terms of our full Privacy Policy.  
\- We typically collect two kinds of information about you: (a) information that you provide that personally identifies you (e.g., full name or phone number); and (b) information that does not personally identify you (e.g., your IP address or type of browser);  
\- This information is transmitted to, held and processed by us in the United States of America;  
\- We typically use this information to provide you with our website and related services, to deliver targeted advertising based on your preferences and our promotions to you, and to produce reports and data about online shopping;  
\- We may disclose this information to authorized third parties including our merchants, advertising and promotional partners and third party service providers for these purposes;  
\- We work with and permit advertising networks to use anonymous information about you for preference or targeted online advertising (see section III below);  
\- You may at any time opt-out of certain activities as set out below (see section VI);  
\- Our websites use "cookies". You can set your browser not to accept cookies if you so wish although this may affect your use of our websites;  
\- We encrypt any information you input using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software and take reasonable security measures to safeguard information;  
\- If you register with us, you have the ability to update or correct the information you previously provided via the account section;  
\- If you have any questions or concerns about privacy at Shopzilla, please contact us by clicking here;  
\- Our websites and our services are not designed or intended for use by children under 13; and  
\- This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check this policy regularly. Any material changes will be notified to you by email as appropriate.

**I. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

We collect two kinds of information related to you: (a) Personally Identifiable Information ("PII"); and (b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information ("Non-PII"). 

**(a) Personally Identifiable Information:** PII includes any information that identifies you as person. We collect your PII when you choose to register with us or when you choose to participate in an interactive feature of our Sites such as a review, survey or promotion. You may: (a) provide your name, mail/shipping address, email address, credit card number and phone number when registering with our Sites or in connection with a contest entry; (b) provide certain demographic information about you (e.g., age, gender, shopping interests and preferences, etc.) when participating in a survey or poll; or (c) post a general comment and/or recommendation on our Sites. 

**(b) Non-Personally Identifiable Information:** Non-PII is any information that does not identify you as a person including PII which has been rendered anonymous. We obtain non-PII either separately or together with your PII as described above. We collect certain non-PII from you when you access our Sites including IP addresses and information relating to your browser, operating system, ISP, the third party website from which your visit originated and how you use our Sites such as the web pages you visit, and the duration of your visits. 

**II. HOW WE USE & SHARE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED**

PII and Non-PII is used to provide, or improve, our Sites and Services to you and to carry out your requests, respond to your inquiries, better serve you and understand your needs, or is used in other ways naturally associated with the circumstances in which you provided the information. 

We may disclose PII and Non-PII to:  
(1) our third party service providers who perform functions on our behalf in connection with the operation of the Sites or Services e.g., providers who host and manage data, process credit card orders, deliver our merchandise, etc; 

(2) participating sponsors to a program or promotion you enter through our Sites or Services; 

(3) our parent company, subsidiaries or other affiliated companies ("affiliated companies") for operational, marketing and promotional purposes; 

(4) co-promotional partners and others with whom we have marketing or other relationships; 

(5) participating merchants where you consent at the time you submit PII to us when using the interactive features of our Sites such as surveys and reviews concerning our participating merchants; and 

(6) our other users where you choose to publicly post reviews, comments or other information relating to products or services, communicate with other users via public forums (e.g., forums, message boards, bulletin boards, etc.).

In addition, we use non-PII to help analyze site traffic, understand customer needs and trends, carry out targeted promotional activities (see "Preference Based Advertising" below). We may use your non-PII by itself or aggregate it with information we have obtained from others to produce research reports and other information and data about online shopping for participating merchants and other customers, as well as media and other interested parties. 

**III. COOKIES AND PREFERENCE BASED ADVERTISING**

**(a) Cookies and Web Beacons:** We automatically receive and store certain types of non-PII whenever you interact with us by using "cookies" and analogous technology. "Cookies" are small files that we place on your computer or your Web browser memory to enable our systems to recognize your browser and to provide convenience and other features to you. **It is important to note that the cookies that we use do not contain and are not tied to PII about you.**

You may be able to direct your internet browser not to allow cookies and you can delete existing cookies from your computer. Please note, however, some elements of our Sites will not function properly or be available to you. 

**(b) Preference Based Advertising:** We work with third parties, including advertising companies and website analysis firms, who use cookies to collect non-PII when you visit our Sites and third party sites about your surfing activities. This non-PII, collected through cookies, is typically used by these third party advertising networks to serve you with advertisements while on third party sites tailored to meet your preferences and likely interests. If you do not wish to participate in this activity, please click here and follow the simple opt-out process. 

A couple of important notes about this opt-out tool: (1) it includes all the advertising networks that Shopzilla works with, but also many that Shopzilla does not work with; and (2) it relies on cookies to ensure that a given advertising network does not collect information about you ("Opt-out Cookies") - for a general explanation of how Opt-out Cookies work, please click here . Therefore, if you buy a new computer, change web browsers or delete these Opt-out Cookies from your computer, you will need to perform the opt-out task again. 

**IV. SALE OF BUSINESS AND DISCLOSURE BY LAW**

**(a) Business Transactions:** We may disclose PII and Non-PII held by us: (a) to a prospective seller or actual seller of any business or assets we acquire; (b) if all or any of our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case, PII and Non-PII may be one of the transferred assets. 

**(b) Required disclosures:** We may disclose and use any PII or non-PII if we are required to do so by law, with respect to copyright and other intellectual property infringement claims, or if we believe that such action is necessary to: (a) fulfill a government request; (b) conform with the requirements of the law or legal process; (c) protect or defend our legal rights or property, our Sites, or other users; or (d) in an emergency to protect the health and safety of our Sites's users or the general public. 

**V. SECURITY OF INFORMATION**

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We also use a secure server hosting location in the US, firewall protection, controlled access and encryption technology to protect your data. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your PII, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your PII. In the unfortunate event that your personally identifiable information is compromised, we will notify you by e-mail to the last e-mail address you have provided us as soon as feasible under the circumstances (delays in notification may occur while we take necessary measures to determine the scope of the breach and restore reasonable integrity to the system, as well as for the legitimate needs of law enforcement if notification would impede a criminal investigation). 

**VI. YOUR OPTIONS & OPT-OUTS**

**(a) What Information Can I Access?** If you register as a Shopzilla member, you will typically have access to an account section that includes the registration information you previously provided which you can update or correct at any time. If there is any inaccurate information that you are not able to correct, just let us know. Also, if you wish, you can delete your membership account entirely although we may retain certain information in limited circumstances - e.g., to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Use . Furthermore, some information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical (e.g., information that is stored in our "back-up" systems) and certain legal constraints. 

**VII. CHILDREN**

As our Sites nor our Services are not intended for use by children under 13, Children under 13 may not submit any PII to us. Also, if you are under 18, you should use Shopzilla and submit information only with involvement of a parent or guardian. 

**VIII. REVISIONS**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time to reflect our changing business practices. We will provide you notice of any such changes by posting the new policy on our Sites or by email if the changes are material. 

**VII. SOLE STATEMENT**

This Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use , both as posted on our Sites and through our Services, contain all of the material terms of regarding your use of our Websites and Services. No summary, modification, restatement or other version thereof, or other privacy statement or policy, in any form, is valid unless we post it to our Sites and Services. 

Feb2012

[Company Valuation](http://www.ebusinessappraisals.com/)  Fast, accurate business appraisals business valuations to sell your business, manage partner buyouts, secure business loans, or manage your business to achieve value for retirement 

[cessione quinto](http://www.cessionequinto-pb.it/) Cessione quinto cessione del v, cessione del quinto dello stipendio, calcolo cessione quinto, cessione quinto inps, cessione del 5, cessione quinto pensione, finanziamenti cessione del quinto, prestiti cessione del quinto, finanziamenti cessione del quinto Cessione quinto Cessione 5

[Payment protection Insurance claims](http://www.paymentprotectionclaim.co.uk/) Admiral wins 9 out 10 Payment Protection Claims (PPI). Reclaim £3,000 in just 60 days for your Payment Protection Claim. Free Phone 0800 862 0571 now. No Win No Fee PPI Claims

[Refinance mortgage rates](http://www.mortgage-refinancing-reviews.com/) Find out which lenders have the best refinamce mortgage interest rates and best deal. You will save thousands. You will be surprised when you see who is the best.

[Bridging finance](http://www.bridging-finance.me.uk/) bridging finance only this is a short term advance which is secured on landed estate or property check out companies that are the actual lenders

[protect your bubble review](http://www.uk-insurance-index.co.uk/protect-your-bubble-car-insurance-3143.html) Until 30 09 11, all new motor insurance policyholders will get a fantastic £40 cash back offer 

March2012

[Esources.co.uk](http://www.wholesalescams.co.uk/esources-co-uk-review)If you want to start up a business online that requires business service whole suppliers, then eSources is one of the UK’s top directories to help you do just that. You can use it to find a whole range of companies in a multitude of different areas, from accounting and finance to recycling facilities.

[Payday Loans Online](http://www.1hourpaydayloansonline.com/) Get fast cash online today! Up to 1500 within an hour no credit checks, no faxing Get money deposited into your account instantly 1 Hour Payday Loans Online

[every day loans](http://www.noworriesloans.org.uk/every-day-loans.html) Every day loans and credit card cash advances essentially serve the same purpose but it is important for consumers to know what short

[long term loans](http://www.24hourloansbadcredit.co.uk/long-term-loans.html) Long term loans as the name specifies are meant for the people who are looking for meeting their long term personal needs.

[Quick Loans Same Day ](http://www.everydayloans.org.uk/quick-loans-same-day.html)Quick loans same day offer the solutions for salaried people till their next payday. These loans are ideal ways to solve the short-term financial problems within same day of applying.

[car insurance](http://www.carinsurancecomparison.com/) Getting car insurance is vital, since they efficiently help in managing the repairs and impairments at the time of damage. Compare the quotes online and find your desired dealer offering best service at affordable cost.

[ETF](https://csetf.com/) Credit Suisse is a leading provider of Exchange Traded Funds in Europe Explore the portfolio of key equity, bond, commodity, theme and regional ETFs here

[clean energy](http://www.frootcase.com/solar-panels/) Solar panels electricity systems also referred to as solar PV or photovoltaic is the most suitable to use especially currently where electric bills are usually high

[Solar panels](http://eurekaiberoamerica.org/solar-panels/) There is a lot of misconception about the effectiveness of the solar PV modules

[cash for gold](http://www.bestpriceforgold.co.uk/) Best Price For Gold is the UK’s leading scrap gold

[Mail Forwarding](http://www.capital-office.co.uk/) : Capital Office provide the most prestigious Virtual Office Services in the UK.  Affordable Mail Forwarding, Virtual Office & PO Box Solutions

may

[PPI Compensation Calculator](http://www.paymentprotectionclaim.co.uk/ppi-claims-calculator.html) Admiral wins 9 out 10 Payment Protection Claims (PPI). Reclaim £3,000 in just 60 days for your Payment Protection Claim.

[Funeral Insurance](http://www.hollardfuneral.co.za/) If you need a funeral plan or burial insurance Hollard funeral are the best. Hollard Funeral provide the best policies with the best terms and claim payments.

[Insurance](http://www.hollard.co.za/) Hollard is a provider of car, household and life insurance. They are one of the leading insurance providers in South Africa.

[Translation Agency London](http://www.translationservices24.com/) We provide professional translation services for companies worldwide. Our professional translation services are reliable, accurate and price competitive.

[EOBR](http://www.ccjdigital.com/category/topical/eobr/) View the most recent newsletter on EOBR and regulate your driver’s hours of operation effectively. Log on to our website now.

[Maximale Hypotheek](http://www.hypotheekadvieshyponu.nl/maximale-hypotheek.html) Met de handige tool van HypoNu kun je direct online berekenen wat je maximale hypotheek is

[Nationstar IPO](http://www.nationstarholdings.com/) We are a leading non-bank residential mortgage servicer with a broad array of servicing capabilities across the residential mortgage product spectrum.  

[security guard services in delhi](http://specialityservices.in/index.php)  Speciality Services:-  Provides service to more than national and Multinational companies catering their Security, Housekeeping & Payrolling Services. Security services in India, Housekeeping services in Delhi.

March2012 | [on line business ideas](http://www.stevenscashflowanswer.com/) | [Executive Leadership](http://www.deprezleadership.com/) | [liberty tax franchise ](http://www.libertytaxvirginia.com/) | [business litigation firm Minneapolis MN](http://www.doylehance.com/business) |[vibration testing equipment](http://www.trilion.com/) | may | [gps fleet managing](http://fleetmanaging101.com/) | [presentation folder](https://www.folderprinters.com/) | [debt management plan  ](http://www.firstunion.co.uk/debt-management.php)| [Top Forex brokers](http://www.forexspace.com/) | [Click here for plastic surgery loans](http://www.unitedmedicalcredit.com/our-services/cosmetic-surgery/)
